# DAINYL JOHN CUA, E.I.T.

2701 Swift Creek Drive

dainylcua@gmail.com

(682)-246-3304

## **Executive Summary**

Highly motivated, quick, critically thinking, and personally accountable worker seeks employment to develop technical skillset in all fields. Experience in the consulting industry has improved soft skills such as communication between international teams in an office and virtual environment, project budgeting, and time management.

## **Employment**

## Staff Engineer

May 2020 - Dec 2020

ALL4 LLC | Houston, TX

- Developed documents for projects with total capital costs ranging from thousands to millions of dollars in a multitude of industries alongside highly capable teams.
- Interpreted complex regulatory language and develop optimized, high-quality files to assist clients maintain emissions limits, recordkeeping requirements, and reporting requirements.
- Interfaced with team members, project managers, and clients to understand expectations and assess feasibility.

#### Sales Associate

Jun 2018 – Aug 2018

Chick-fil-A | Burleson, TX

- Greeted customers and provided an enjoyable experience during their stay at the restaurant.
- Worked in a fast-paced environment under stress, maintaining short wait times and occasionally working outside to move drive-thru line along.
- Maintained a flexible work schedule and came into the restaurant multiple times when under-staffed.

#### Education

## Texas A&M University | College Station, TX

Aug 2016 - May 2020

Chemical Engineering – Bachelor of Science in Engineering GPA: 3.594

#### Certification

American Institute of Chemical Engineers – Safety and Chemical Engineering Education Level 1 Engineer In Training Certification

### Skills

Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint Proficient in MATLAB

• Created a variable temperature Pourbaix diagram that displays conditions which cause corrosion in multiple types of metals.

Familiar with Aspen Plus, ProMax

 Assisted in development of a triethylaluminum plant alongside a college team for a sponsored semester-long project.

Familiar with AutoCAD, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, React Native, JSX, Node.js, Git